Guide to the Poles in Western Pennsylvania Collection, 1910s-1990s AIS.1965.16
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Wars and Polish Veterans, V.
  - Borkowski, Joseph, III.
    - Correspondence: 1965 - 1967; 1968; 1969, Jan - Mar; 1969, Apr - Dec; 1970; 1971; 1972, Jan - June; 1972, July - Dec; 1973; 1974; 1975; 1976 - 1979; 1980 - 1984; 1985 - 1987; 1988 - 1990; 1992 - 1993; St. Stanislavs Kostha; Lawrenceville Catholic High School; Wingfield Family; Revolutionary War Veterans (Box 7)
    - Manuscripts of Articles: A - J; K - O; P - R; Polish Organizations, Societies, etc.; Writings, Our Heritage; S - Z; History of the Central Council of Polish organizations in Pittsburgh; Polish Fraternals in Allegheny County; Fragments; Writings, Books Reviews (Box 8)
  - Programs, Events and Activities, VI.
    - Church Dedications/Anniversaries; Debutante's Ball; Polish American Day; Polish Day and Polish Day Picnic (Box 11)
    - Miscellaneous Pamietnik; Miscellaneous Programs (alphabetical) (Box 12)
- Publications and Books, VII.
  - Clippings and Publications (in alphabetical order); Joseph Borkowski's News Clippings (Box 12)
  - Publications, cont. (in alphabetical order) (Box 13)
    - Pittsburczanin (last issue published), January 21, 1972
  - Misc. Books and Publications in Polish; Publications by Poles Outside Poland and the U.S. (Box 14)
  - Church Publications; Liturgy; Prayerbooks; Bibles (Box 15)
- Videotapes and Film, VIII.
  - Five items (Box 17)
- Scrapbooks and Photos, IX.
  - Alliance College Scrapbooks (Box 16-16A, 18-21)
  - Picture Remnant of Unknown Gathering, ZPRK (Polish Roman Catholic Union) (Map-case 7-1)
  - Picture, 42nd Conference, Polish Roman Catholic Union, Wilkes-Barre, PA (Map-case 7-1)